It will not take much time for the market to reach 23000.
First break 22500, then
break 22650. You may
even reach 2000 in three days. So, someone might be thinking
that did you say 23000? Oh, such a big
level is not such a big level, the market has
demonstrated it in front of you. So,
Aditya Arora has put before you a broad
index viewpoint. Let's
start with stocks with Ayush Mehta. Ayush Sir,
good morning, tell me Sir, which are your stocks today?
Good morning, Mr. Good
morning, Abhishek Ji, and good morning to
all the viewers, panelists. There will be two buy calls from my side.
I feel that there has been
selling in mid-cap and small-cap stocks, but a
small but stock-specific buying is being
seen in the stocks, but I like the
intellect from here. If
we talk about intellect here, then
we see a good formation of higher top, higher bottom on
all its time frames. There is a
positive RSI crossover. The
stock has held its position for a long time,
plus all  This stock is trading above the averages,
plus we will see a big rally in it
in a short time. So I think I should
buy ICI from here for a
target of 1160. Here you have to maintain a stop loss of
1095 and as soon as this stock
crosses 1135, it will start a big rally. The
second stock of mine is ICI
General Insurance. Talking about ICI,
even in such a falling market, the stock has held
itself well.
With the support of the 20-day moving average, the stock has been
straddling for many days and is closing above it. There is a
formation of a pullback pattern in its weekly and monthly charts.
Plus, a breakout of cluster resistance is
visible
in its intraday 60-minute chart. So I
think ICI General Insurance should be bought from here
for a target of 1740.
Here, your stop loss will be 1625,
which is its previous
support design and ICC Lombard. These two
recommendations from Ayush, Aditya, are
on your radar.  Which stocks are you recommending to trade
today? Look, a stock came on my radar today which is
a fairly stable stock. There is not much volatility
because the market is volatile right now.
So I
would like to go with some stable stocks. The name of the stock is 3M
India. We can buy it at 38. The
stop loss will be 29,900 and the target will be 32,000 to 33,000.
India Sir, are you offering only one
stock? Aditya Sir, are you
offering only one 3M India right now? But I
think there will be
many opportunities tomorrow and the day after tomorrow. So, of course,
I also like financials and
top bank names. But today I had just
prepared a stock which seemed good.
Sir, one stock will do. One stock is so
heavy that it is equal to three or four. No problem.
But still, please write down the target for 3M India once. Do
you have any idea about the volume etc. in it?
Aditya ji, how much volume would there be in THM India?
I have not checked the exact figure,
but the volume is a little low.
Because the size of the stock is very big, so
yesterday my volume figure was 3.6 quantity,
that is 3500 shares, so roughly you can
understand that the quantum is big, the volume is less
and if it works then it can give good profit,
calculation of 10 shares of 700-750 means
000 anna, I am telling you simply, so
your target is 32000, this is 2000
points above, so 10 shares will be created at 1000 points,
0000, so this is a contract of 00,
if you calculate with 10 shares then
put a stop loss of 29900, stop loss
is small, risk range, okay, done
Aditya, we have noticed your share,
ICS Lombard has become an Intellect
Design, these two shares
are Ayush Mehta's shares, one of these IT
shares also came, Santosh Sir, good morning, I hope
you are able to hear the voice well, Sir,
first tell me about your shares, then I
also have a couple of questions  I will take your answer to that. Yes,
good morning, sorry, there was a slight
network issue, so I am on the buying side,
I would like to focus on L&K. First, my
TCS will be a buy. You can see that this
volume is heating up. Right now there is
a good breakout of a flag formation in IT stocks. I
think more bullishness can happen, as per which
yesterday overnight again the market
saw a rise, so the target here will be 4300. The
stop loss will be 4150.
Second, my MNM is there, there was a small
correction here, the stock took support at its 20 day
moving edge yesterday. It seems that
MNM is
22500 sir, I will write it because your
levels and my levels have almost matched.
22200 22500. Hey, please show Bank Nifty also.
Sir, he has given a trade of his Bank Nifty.
Show Bank Nifty also. Viewers should also
note what is Santosh Sir's trade in
it. Yours is fine within Bank Nifty.
47800 sir, ours has also matched.
47800 is your target too and 46900
is just a difference of 100 points, no problem,
go long M&M share on Nifty and Bank Nifty,
you have given a good one, apart from this we have
collected all the shares, Theme India IS, Lord Intellect Design, these are some shares, okay sir, let me enquire about one share from
you, Sir HG